How dare you!
(Leonard:)Listen, I should warn you
(Leonard:)that maybe asking Amy out
isn't a good idea.
(Sheldon:)Barry, a word?
(Leonard:)And now the crazy version
of what I just said.
(Sheldon:)If you intend to pursue Amy,
(Sheldon:)you leave me with no choice
but to put a stop to it.
(Barry:)And how are you gonna do that?
(Sheldon:)By challenging you to a duel.
You've had one lesson.
I'll destroy you.
(Sheldon:)That is why
the duel will take place
(Sheldon:)at high noon,
three years from today.
(Sheldon:)If you're worth your salt
as an instructor,
(Sheldon:)I should be ready by then.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, and be warned.
(Sheldon:)I'm going to touch you all over.
Wow. That-that was crazier
than I thought.
(Penny:)All right,
I'm not saying